<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sireum</title>
    <link>https://sireum.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sireum</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://sireum.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sireum.org/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sireum.org/home/</guid>
      <description>Sireum aims to provide basic building blocks, frameworks, and tools to engineer high assurance systems by employing various formal method techniques for system validation and verification (V&amp;amp;V) at different stages of system development cycle such as architectural designs and system implementations.
Read more &amp;hellip;
(c) 2017-2023, SAnToS Lab, Kansas State University, contact@santoslab.org</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://sireum.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sireum.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Sireum aims to provide basic building blocks, frameworks, and tools to engineer high assurance systems by employing various formal method techniques for system validation and verification (V&amp;amp;V) at different stages of system development cycle such as architectural designs and system implementations.
Central to its approach is Slang &amp;ndash; the Sireum programming language, a modern language designed first for formal safety and security analyses. Slang is (currently) realized as a subset of the Scala programming language with customized semantics designed to ease program reasoning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funding</title>
      <link>https://sireum.org/funding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sireum.org/funding/</guid>
      <description>MAILLE: Microkernal Application Information fLow with Logic-based Enforcement
John Hatcliff (K-State PI), Robby; and Todd Carpenter (Lead PI) at Adventium Labs
U.S. Air Force Research Laboratory (AFRL) Small Business Innovation Research (SBIR) Phase II
Project total: $749,957 (K-State&#39;s portion: $347,000)
Duration: May 2021 - April 2023 SIRFUR: Software Implementation from Rigorous Formal Usable Requirements
Robby (K-State PI), John Hatcliff; and Todd Carpenter (Lead PI) at Adventium Labs
Defense Advanced Research Projects Agency (DARPA) Small Business Innovation Research (SBIR) Phase II</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://sireum.org/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sireum.org/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Sireum is available as pre-built binaries/installers or from source. The main advantage of using the source distribution is that updates can be done incrementally while the binary distribution requires complete re-installation. On the other hand, source distribution requires more setup. As Sireum is currently in its early active development phase, it is highly recommended to use the source distribution.
Download Binary Distributions GitHub Releases The binary distribution files are available at: https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papers</title>
      <link>https://sireum.org/papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sireum.org/papers/</guid>
      <description>Jason Belt, John Hatcliff, Robby, John Shackleton, Jim Carciofini, Todd Carpenter, Eric Mercer, Isaac Amundson, Junaid Babar, Darren Cofer, David Hardin, Karl Hoech, Konrad Slind, Ihor Kuz, Kent McLeod: Model-driven development for the seL4 microkernel using the HAMR framework. JSA 134: 102789, 2023. John Hatcliff, Danielle Stewart, Jason Belt, Robby: An AADL Contract Language Supporting Integrated Model- and Code-Level Verification. HILT 2022 (to appear). Darren Cofer, Isaac Amundson, Junaid Babar, David Hardin, Konrad Slind, Perry Alexander, John Hatcliff, Robby, Gerwin Klein, Corey Lewis, Eric Mercer, John Shackleton: Cyberassured Systems Engineering at Scale.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
