<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sireum</title>
    <link>https://sireum.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sireum</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://sireum.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://sireum.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sireum.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Sireum aims to provide basic building blocks, frameworks, and tools to engineer high assurance systems by employing various formal method techniques for system validation and verification (V&amp;V) at different stages of system development cycle such as architectural designs and system implementations. Central to its approach is Slang &amp;ndash; the Sireum programming language, a modern language designed first for formal safety and security analyses. Slang is (currently) realized as a subset of the Scala programming language with customized semantics designed to ease program reasoning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funding</title>
      <link>https://sireum.org/funding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sireum.org/funding/</guid>
      <description>SIRFUR: Software Implementation from Rigorous Formal Usable Requirements&#xA;Robby (K-State PI), John Hatcliff; and Todd Carpenter (Lead PI) at Adventium Labs&#xA;Defense Advanced Research Projects Agency (DARPA) Small Business Innovation Research (SBIR) Phase II&#xA;Project total: $1,499,766 (K-State&#39;s portion: $693,000)&#xA;Duration: October 2020 - September 2023 MAILLE: Microkernal Application Information fLow with Logic-based Enforcement&#xA;John Hatcliff (K-State PI), Robby; and Todd Carpenter (Lead PI) at Adventium Labs&#xA;U.S. Air Force Research Laboratory (AFRL) Small Business Innovation Research (SBIR) Phase II</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://sireum.org/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sireum.org/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Sireum can be retrieved using installers, packaged binaries, or from source. The main advantage of using the source distribution is that updates can be done incrementally while the binary distribution requires complete re-installation. On the other hand, source distribution requires more setup. The source distribution should be used by Sireum developers and code contributors, while users are recommended to use the installer scripts, or download from Sireum&amp;rsquo;s GitHub Releases.&#xA;Note that, the latest pre-built binary installed by the scripts might be behind the latest source commit, but it does not require source compilation (faster).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAMR SysML v2</title>
      <link>https://sireum.org/hamr-sysmlv2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sireum.org/hamr-sysmlv2/</guid>
      <description>SysML is a standardized modeling language used throughout industry for systems engineering &amp;ndash; particularly for embedded systems. The Object Management Group (OMG) is developing a new version of SysML referred to as SysMLv2. Instead of SysML modeling concepts being shoe-horned into UML as a UML profile, SysMLv2 has been reengineered from its foundations to provide a cleaner and more rigorous presentation of system modeling concepts. It has adopted features that have been central to AADL for decades &amp;ndash; the most notable are: (a) the inclusion of companion textual and graphical views of a model, and (b) a much greater focus on model semantics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrated Verification Environment (IVE)</title>
      <link>https://sireum.org/ive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sireum.org/ive/</guid>
      <description>[pending]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papers</title>
      <link>https://sireum.org/papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sireum.org/papers/</guid>
      <description>Robby, John Hatcliff, Jason Belt: Logika: The Sireum Verification Framework. FMICS 2024 (to appear). Stefan Hallerstede, John Hatcliff, Robby: Teaching with Logika: Conceiving and Constructing Correct Software. FMTea 2024 (to appear). John Hatcliff, Jason Belt, Robby, David Hardin: Integrated Contract-based Unit and System Testing for Component-based Systems. NFM 2024: 406-426. John Hatcliff, Robby, Jason Belt, Jacob Legg, Danielle Stewart, Todd Carpenter: Automated Property-based Testing from AADL Component Contracts. FMICS 2023: 131-150.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://sireum.org/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sireum.org/team/</guid>
      <description>Faculty&#xA;Robby: Principal Architect &amp;amp; Engineer, Slang and Logika Lead John Hatcliff: HAMR, Documentation Lead, and External Liaison Coordinator Research Associates&#xA;Jason Belt: Main HAMR Developer Graduate Students&#xA;Ben Thompson: Slang-to-Rust Translation Undergraduate Students&#xA;Gage Hawbaker: HAMR System Exemplars Jacob Legg: HAMR and Slang Testing Framework Clint McKenzie: HAMR High School Students&#xA;Catalina Liang: HAMR, Webmaster, and Documentation Collaborators Aarhus University&#xA;Faculty&#xA;Stefan Hallerstede: Slang Embedded-to-Rust Translation, Logika course materials, Isabelle integration Collins Aerospace</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
